Privacy Policy
==============

This document was last updated on Nov 17, 2021

Introduction
------------

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how Website Operator (“Website Operator”, “we”, “us” or “our”) collects, protects and uses the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you (“User”, “you” or “your”) may provide on the **dogfluffy.com** website and any of its products or services (collectively, “Website” or “Services”).

It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your Personal Information and how you can access and update this information.

This Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control, or to individuals that we do not employ or manage.

Automatic Collection Of Information
-----------------------------------

When you visit the Website our servers automatically record information that your browser sends. This data may include information such as your device’s IP address, browser type and version, operating system type and version, language preferences or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Website, pages of our Website that you visit, the time spent on those pages, the information you search for on our Website, access times and dates, and other statistics.

Information collected automatically is used only to identify potential cases of abuse and establish statistical information regarding Website usage.

This statistical information is not otherwise aggregated in such a way that it would identify any particular user of the system.

Collection Of Personal Information
----------------------------------

You can visit the Website without telling us who you are or revealing any information by which someone could identify you as a specific, identifiable individual.

If, however, you wish to use some of the Website’s features, you will be asked to provide certain Personal Information (for example, **your [name](https://www.dogfluffy.com/female-american-bulldog-names)** and **e-mail address**). We receive and store any information you knowingly provide to us when you create an account, publish content, make a purchase, or fill any online forms on the Website. When required, this information may include the following:

– **Personal details** such as [name](https://www.dogfluffy.com/female-american-bulldog-names), country of residence, etc.  
– **Contact information** such as email address, address, etc.  
– **Account details** such as user [name](https://www.dogfluffy.com/swedish-dog-names/), [unique](https://www.dogfluffy.com/101-dalmatians-dog-names) user ID, password, etc.  
– **Proof of identity** such as a photocopy of a government ID.  
– **Payment information** such as credit card details, bank details, etc.  
– **Information about other individuals** such as your [family](https://www.dogfluffy.com/fluffy-dogs-for-families) members, friends, etc.  
– **Any other materials** you willingly submit to us such as articles, images, feedback, etc.

You can choose not to provide us with your **Personal Information**, but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Website’s features. Users who are uncertain about what information is mandatory are welcome to [contact us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/).

Managing Personal Information
-----------------------------

You are able to delete certain Personal Information we have about you. The Personal Information you can delete may change as the Website or Services change.

When you delete Personal Information, however, we may maintain a copy of the unrevised Personal Information in our records for the duration necessary to comply with our obligations to our affiliates and partners, and for the purposes described below.

If you would like to delete your Personal Information or permanently delete your account, you can do so on the settings page of your account on the Website or simply by [contacting us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/).

Storing Personal Information
----------------------------

We will retain and use your Personal Information for the period necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.

We may use any aggregated data derived from or incorporating your Personal Information after you update or delete it, but not in a manner that would identify you personally.

Once the retention period expires, Personal Information shall be deleted. Therefore, the right to access, the right to erasure, the right to rectification, and the right to data portability cannot be enforced after the expiration of the retention period.

Use And Processing Of Collected Information
-------------------------------------------

In order to make our Website and Services available to you, or to meet a legal obligation, we need to collect and use certain Personal Information. If you do not provide the information that we request, we may not be able to provide you with the requested products or services. Some of the information we collect is directly from you via our Website. However, we may also collect Personal Information about you from other sources such as social media, emails, etc. Any of the information we collect from you may be used for the following purposes:

– Create and manage user accounts  
– Fulfill and manage orders  
– Deliver products or services  
– Improve products and services  
– Send administrative information  
– Send marketing and promotional communications  
– Respond to inquiries and offer support  
– Request user feedback  
– Improve user experience  
– Post customer testimonials  
– Deliver targeted advertising  
– Administer prize draws and competitions  
– Enforce terms and conditions and policies  
– Protect from abuse and malicious users  
– Respond to legal requests and prevent harm  
– Run and operate our Website and Services

Processing your Personal Information depends on how you interact with our Website, where you are located in the world and if one of the following applies:

(i) You have given your consent for one or more specific purposes. This, however, does not apply, whenever the processing of Personal Information is subject to the California Consumer Privacy Act or European data protection law;  
(ii) Provision of information is necessary for the performance of an agreement with you and/or for any pre-contractual obligations thereof;  
(iii) Processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which you are subject;  
(iv) Processing is related to a task that is carried out in the public interest or in the [exercise](https://www.dogfluffy.com/labrador-retriever-dog-breed-information) of official authority vested in us;  
(v) Processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party.

Note that under some legislations we may be allowed to process information until you object to such processing (by opting out), without having to rely on consent or any other of the following legal bases below. In any case, we will be [happy](https://www.dogfluffy.com/can-dogs-eat-raw-chicken) to clarify the specific legal basis that applies to the processing, and in particular whether the provision of Personal Information is a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.

Information Transfer And Storage
--------------------------------

Depending on your location, data transfers may involve transferring and storing your information in a country other than your own.

You are entitled to learn about the legal basis of information transfers to a country [outside](https://www.dogfluffy.com/dog-window-guard) the **European Union** or to any international organization governed by public international law or set up by two or more countries, such as the **UN**, and about the security measures taken by us to safeguard your information.

If any such transfer takes place, you can find out more by checking the relevant sections of this document or inquire with us using the information provided in the contact section.

The Rights Of Users
-------------------

You may [exercise](https://www.dogfluffy.com/labrador-retriever-dog-breed-information) certain rights regarding your information processed by us. In particular, you have the right to do the following:

**(i)** you have the right to withdraw consent where you have previously given your consent to the processing of your information;  
**(ii)** you have the right to object to the processing of your information if the processing is carried out on a legal basis other than consent;  
**(iii)** you have the right to learn if the information is being processed by us, obtain disclosure regarding certain aspects of the processing and obtain a copy of the information undergoing processing;  
**(iv)** you have the right to verify the accuracy of your information and ask for it to be updated or corrected;  
**(v)** you have the right, under certain circumstances, to restrict the processing of your information, in which case, we will not process your information for any purpose other than storing it;  
**(vi)** you have the right, under certain circumstances, to obtain the erasure of your Personal Information from us;  
**(vii)** you have the right to receive your information in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and, if technically feasible, to have it transmitted to another controller without any hindrance.

This provision is applicable provided that your information is processed by automated means and that the processing is based on your consent, on a contract which you are part of or on pre-contractual obligations thereof.

The Right To Object To Processing
---------------------------------

Where Personal Information is processed for the public interest, in the [exercise](https://www.dogfluffy.com/labrador-retriever-dog-breed-information) of an official authority vested in us or for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us, you may object to such processing by providing a ground related to your particular situation to justify the objection.

You [must know](https://www.dogfluffy.com/pomeranian-and-yorkie-mix/) that, however, should your Personal Information be processed for direct marketing purposes, you can object to that processing at any time without providing any justification.

To learn, whether we are processing Personal Information for direct marketing purposes, you may refer to the relevant sections of this document.

How To Exercise These Rights
----------------------------

Any requests to [exercise](https://www.dogfluffy.com/labrador-retriever-dog-breed-information) User rights can be directed to Website Operator through the contact details provided in this document.

These requests can be exercised free of charge and will be addressed by Website Operator as early as possible.

California Privacy Rights
-------------------------

In addition to the rights as explained in this Privacy Policy, California residents who provide Personal Information (as defined in the statute) to obtain products or services for personal, [family](https://www.dogfluffy.com/fluffy-dogs-for-families), or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us, once a calendar year, information about the Personal Information we shared, if any, with other businesses for marketing uses.

If applicable, this information would include the categories of Personal Information and the [names](https://www.dogfluffy.com/female-american-bulldog-names) and addresses of those businesses with which we shared such personal information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in the current year will receive information about the prior year). To obtain this information please [contact us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/).

Billing And Payments
--------------------

In case of services requiring **payment**, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments.

**Your purchase** transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.

Where necessary for processing future **payments** and subject to your prior consent, your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of our reputed payment gateway service provider who is beholden to treating your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

All direct **payment gateways** adhere to the latest security standards as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express, and Discover.

[Sensitive](https://www.dogfluffy.com/american-bulldog-pulling-harness) and private data exchange happens over an **SSL secured communication** channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures, and our Website is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

Scans for malware are performed on a regular basis for additional security and protection.

Product And Service Providers
-----------------------------

We may contract with other companies to provide certain **products and services**. These service providers are not authorized to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements.

We may share Personal Information for these purposes only with **third parties** whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to Personal Information Our **service** providers are given the information they need to perform their designated functions, and we do not authorize them to use or disclose Personal Information for their own marketing or other purposes.

Privacy Of Children
-------------------

We do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from [children](https://www.dogfluffy.com/are-corgis-good-with-cats) under the [age](https://www.dogfluffy.com/dog-tooth-brush) of 13. If you are under the [age](https://www.dogfluffy.com/dog-tooth-brush) of 13, please do not submit any Personal Information through our Website or Service. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce this Policy by instructing their [children](https://www.dogfluffy.com/are-corgis-good-with-cats) never to provide Personal Information through our Website or Service without their permission.

If you have reason to believe that a child under the [age](https://www.dogfluffy.com/dog-tooth-brush) of 13 has provided Personal Information to us through our Website or Service, please [contact us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/). You must also be at least 16 years of [age](https://www.dogfluffy.com/dog-tooth-brush) to consent to the processing of your Personal Information in your country (in some countries we may allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf).

Newsletters
-----------

We offer electronic newsletters to which you may voluntarily subscribe at any time. We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential and will not disclose your email address to any third parties except as allowed in the information use and processing section or for the purposes of utilizing a third-party provider to send such emails. We will maintain the information sent via e-mail in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mails sent from us will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on [how to](https://www.manualtut.com/tag/how-to "how to") contact the sender. You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or by [contacting us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/). However, you will continue to receive essential transactional emails.

Cookies
-------

The Website uses “**cookies**” to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

We may use cookies to collect, store, and track information for statistical purposes to operate our Website and Services. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the Website and Services. To learn more about cookies and how to manage them, visit internetcookies.org

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third-party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on the Website. These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user [behavior](https://www.dogfluffy.com/labrador-retriever-male-vs-female).

Do Not Track Signals
--------------------

Some browsers incorporate a Do Not Track feature that signals to websites you visit that you do not want to have your online [activity](https://www.dogfluffy.com/how-big-is-a-mini-goldendoodle) tracked. Tracking is not the same as using or collecting information in connection with a website.

For these purposes, tracking refers to collecting personally identifiable information from consumers who use or visit a website or online service as they move across different websites over time.

Our Website does not track its visitors over time and across third-party websites. However, some third-party sites may [keep track](https://www.dogfluffy.com/can-i-put-a-tracking-chip-in-my-dog) of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you.

Advertisement
-------------

We may display online advertisements and we may share aggregated and non-identifying information about our customers that we collect through the registration process or through online surveys and promotions with certain advertisers.

We do not share personally identifiable information about individual customers with advertisers.

In some instances, we may use this aggregated and non-identifying information to deliver tailored advertisements to the intended audience.

Do Not Sell My Personal Information
-----------------------------------

You have the right to opt-out of the sale of Your personal information. Once We receive and confirm a verifiable consumer request from You, we will stop selling Your personal information. To [exercise](https://www.dogfluffy.com/labrador-retriever-dog-breed-information) Your right to opt-out, please [contact Us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/).

The Service Providers we partner with (for example, our analytics or advertising partners) may use technology on the Service that sells personal information as defined by the CCPA law. If you wish to opt out of the use of Your personal information for interest-based advertising purposes and these potential sales as defined under CCPA law, you may do so by following the instructions below.

Please note that any opt out is specific to the browser You use. You may need to opt out on every browser that You use.

Affiliates
----------

We may disclose information about you to our affiliates for the purpose of being able to offer you related or additional products and services.

Any information relating to you that we provide to our affiliates will be treated by those affiliates in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Links To Other Websites
-----------------------

Our Website contains links to other websites that are not owned or controlled by us.

Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites or third-parties.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that may collect Personal Information.

Information Security
--------------------

We secure information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical, and [physical](https://www.dogfluffy.com/exercise-equipment-for-your-bulldog) safeguards in an effort to protect against unauthorized access, use, modification, and disclosure of Personal Information in its control and custody.

However, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed.

Therefore, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that

**(i)** there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control;  
**(ii)** the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and our Website cannot be guaranteed; and  
**(iii)** any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third-party, despite [best](https://www.dogfluffy.com/can-dogs-eat-raw-chicken) efforts.

Data Breach
-----------

In the [event](https://www.dogfluffy.com/fluffy-dog-events) we become aware that the security of the Website has been compromised or users Personal Information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external [activity](https://www.dogfluffy.com/how-big-is-a-mini-goldendoodle), including, but not limited to, security attacks or fraud, we reserve the right to take reasonably appropriate measures, including, but not limited to, investigation and reporting, as well as notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities.

In the [event](https://www.dogfluffy.com/fluffy-dog-events) of a data breach, we will make reasonable efforts to notify affected individuals if we believe that there is a reasonable risk of harm to the user as a result of the breach or if notice is otherwise required by law.

When we do, we will post a notice on the Website, send you an email, get in touch with you over the phone, mail you a letter.

Legal Disclosure
----------------

We will disclose any information we collect, use or receive if required or permitted by law, such as to comply with a Subpoena or similar legal process, and when we believe in [good](https://www.dogfluffy.com/lifespan-of-a-chihuahua) faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your [safety](https://www.dogfluffy.com/zipline-harness-for-dogs) or the [safety](https://www.dogfluffy.com/zipline-harness-for-dogs) of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

Changes And Amendments
----------------------

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in our discretion and will notify you of any [material](https://www.dogfluffy.com/dog-window-guard) changes to the way in which we [treat](https://www.dogfluffy.com/french-bulldog-bad-breath) Personal Information.

When changes are made, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We may also provide notice to you in other ways in our discretion, such as through contact information you have provided.

Any updated version of this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy unless otherwise specified.

Your continued use of the Website or Services after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy (or such other act specified at that time) will constitute your consent to those changes.

However, we will not, without your consent, use your Personal Data in a manner materially different than what was stated at the time your Personal Data was collected.

Acceptance Of This Policy
-------------------------

You acknowledge that you have read this Policy and agree to all its terms and conditions.

By using the Website or its Services you agree to be bound by this Policy.

If you do not agree to abide by the terms of this Policy, you are not authorized to use or access the Website and its Services.

Contacting Us
-------------

If you would like to [contact us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/) to understand more about this Policy or wish to [contact us](https://www.dogfluffy.com/contact-fluffy/) concerning any matter relating to individual rights and your Personal Information, you may do so via the contact form or send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.dogfluffy.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Latest posts
------------

    ### [French Bulldog Raw Diet: Best Tips and Benefits for Your Pup](https://www.dogfluffy.com/french-bulldog-raw-diet)

    ### [Best Dog Food for Fluffy Frenchies: Top Picks for Health and Happiness](https://www.dogfluffy.com/best-dog-food-for-fluffy-frenchies)

    ### [Best Fluffy Frenchie Grooming Tools for Stress-Free Pet Care](https://www.dogfluffy.com/fluffy-frenchie-grooming-tools)

#### Pages

#### Fluffy Guides

#### About us

Are you ready to unleash the secrets of a happy and healthy dog? Look no further! Our blog, Dog Fluffy, is your ultimate guide to all things canine.

Explore our blog posts below to discover more about the wonderful world of Fluffy dogs!

#### Get in Touch

Mustafa Kamal St., 11,  
14552 Alexandria

[\[email protected\]](https://www.dogfluffy.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

#### Affiliate Disclaimer

As an Amazon Associate, we earn from qualifying purchases.

© 2024

Made with Love
